Oh, is that your girlfriend?
あ、彼女さんですか?
that's right.
そうです
Oh, hello, hello.
あー、どうもどうもどうも
Thank you for your help.
どうもお世話になります
nice to meet you.
初めまして
Ah, the app.
あ、アプリの
Ah, thank you for your help.
あ、お世話になりました
As for the app.
アプリの方では
Hello, hello, hello.
どう もどうもどうもどうも
It's a true story, though.
実話なんですけどね
Actually, I was shown it on TV.
実はあの、テレビとかで見せてもらってたんですよ
Ah, thank you very much.
あ、ありがとうございます
That's right, that's right.
なんかその、そうなんですよ、そうなんですよ
I was wondering if I could get a reply if I said it on the app.
アプリで言ったらちょっと返信届くおるかなって思って
So, you stopped doing it, right?
で、その、やめちゃったじゃないですか
Yes, yes.
うん、はい
Why did they stop paying taxes again?
なんでまたその、税のやめちゃったんすかね
Wow, it was a little better.
すごい少しよかったのに
Oh, is that your girlfriend?
あ、彼女さんですか?
that's right.
そうです
Oh, hello, hello.
あー、どうもどうもどうも
Thank you for your help.
どうもお世話になります
nice to meet you.
初めまして
of the app.
アプリの
Ah, thank you for your help.
あ、お世話になりました
As for the app.
アプリの方では
Hello, hello, hello.
どう もどうもどうもどうも
Um, didn't she make a promise on the app?
あのー、彼女さん、アプリで約束したじゃないですか
Um, here I am, from now on, with my uncle.
あのー、ここね、これから、おじさんと、
Is it okay if I say you'll hold the Nakata City New Year's party?
中田市新年会、やってくれるって感じでいいですか?
OK?
大丈夫 ですか?
Understood.
分かりました
You look really happy.
ちゃんと嬉しそうっすね
I have no choice.
しかないと
Well then, let's go to the hotel, shall we?
じゃあ、ホテルこっちになるんで行きましょうか
Yes, please.
はい、お願いします
はい、 お願いします
Well, it's a hotel.
どうよ、ホテルですね
Well, I was shown it on TV or something.
ちょっとあの、テレビとかで見せてもらってたんですよ
Ah, thank you very much.
あ、ありがとうございます
That's right, that's right.
なんかそのー、そうなんですよ、そうなんですよ
I was wondering if I would get a reply if I said it on the app.
アプリで言ったら、ちょっと返信届くおるかなって思って
So, you quit, didn't you?
で、その、辞めちゃったじゃないですか
Ah, yes.
あー、はい
Why did you quit the entertainment industry again?
なんでまたその、芸能辞めちゃったんすかね
Wow, I was feeling great.
すごい、こう、ね、調子良かったのに
Any new goals?
なんか、新しい目標?
Yes, yes.
はい、はい
So, I quit.
で、辞めちゃいました
I see.
なるほど
What?
え、なんすか?
What are your new goals?
新しい目標は?
Starting in the spring, we will move on from billing to medical care.
春から、料計の方を進んで、 医療に、
Let's do our best.
頑張ろうかな
I see.
なるほど
But it's a piece of sincerity.
でも真心の塊っすね
got it.
わかりました
I'm going to share a little bit with young people who are heading towards their dreams.
ちょっと 夢に向かった若者に、ちょっとこれからぶち込まします
So.
んで
Well then, let's go to the hotel.
じゃあ、 ホテルこっちなんで行きましょう
Are you thinking of going?
行っちゃいそうなの?
What, did you go?
なに、行っちゃったの?
What, does it feel good to have a vibrator thrust into you?
なに、バイブ突っ込まれて気持ちいいの?
Yeah.
うん